Guide to the Jeffrey S. Lehman papers, 2003-2005.
Lehman, Jeffrey S. papers,2003-2005
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Jeffrey S. Lehman papers, 2003-2005.
3-14-3395
Jeffrey S. Lehman
5.5 cubic ft.
Speeches
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Miscellaneous papers from the President's Office, including speeches. Also, "Reflections on the Call to Engagement," October 2004.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
President of Cornell University, 2003-2005.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Miscellaneous papers from the President's Office, including speeches. Also, "Reflections on the Call to Engagement," October 2004.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Lehman, Jeffrey S.; Lehman, Jeffrey S.; Cornell University. President.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin. Consult the University Archivist.
The Cornell University Archives Web Archive has a collection copies of speeches and essays given by President Lehman here, click on Archives: https://wayback.archive-it.org/2566/20140615215452/http://cornell-classic.univcomm.cornell.edu/president/history_bio_lehman.cfm#
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I: Speeches
  - JSL Acceptance of C.U. Presidency, December 14, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Community Fireworks Show, July 2, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Community Development Society Meeting, July 20, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cornell's Transnational Mission, July 24, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - International Students PREPARE Dinner, August 18, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - POST Closing Dinner Picnic, August 21, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tatkon Center Events, August 22, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Parent and Legacy Reception, August 23, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Convocation Address, August 23, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Cornell in the Berkshires, August 24, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CITE Diversity Initiative, August 26, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Abroad Reception, September 2, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Flexible Display Center Site Visit, September 2, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Welcome to Cornell Video Script, September, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Reunion Kick-off Reception, September 5, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Presidential Councilors, September 8, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Dinner with Charles and Ilda Lee, September 10, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Architecture Art and Planning Advisory Council Breakfast, September 12, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - White Hall Dedication, September 12, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - A&S Advisory Council Meeting, September 12, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Blanche Goldenberg F. B. Luncheon, September 12, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - EPE Program, Sheila C. Johnson Introduction, September 16, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Engineering Fall Faculty Reception, September 18, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 21st Annual Real Estate Conference, September 19, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - New Faculty Orientation, September 19, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Tang Cornell China Scholars Program Celebration, September 19, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Engineers Without Frontiers, September 19, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Jane R. Harrison F.B. Ceremony, September 20, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Dinner Hosted by Andrew H. and Ann R. Tisch, September 22, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Dinner Hosted by Stephen and Suzanne Weiss, September 23, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Cornell Club Luncheon and Reception, September 24, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - President's Statement on Affirmative Action, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Dinner to Honor Hatfield Fellow James C. Morgan, 10/02/03 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Academic and Student Program Professionals Meeting, 10/02/03 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Law School Advisory Council Annual Meeting, 10/03/03 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Local Leaders Football Brunch, 10/04/03 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - AGORA Launch Quote, 10/08/03 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - President's Message, Engineering Awards Booklet, 10/2003 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - First Inaugural Address as President, Doha, Qatar, 10/12/03 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Inaugural Events, Qatar Education City Launch, 10/13/03 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Inaugural Events, Press Briefing, 10/15/03 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Inaugural Events, Cornell in New York City - ILR Extension, 10/15/03 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Inaugural Event New York City Engagement, 10/15/03 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Tompkins County Library Event, 10/16/03 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Zinck's Night Video Taping, 10/16/03 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Statement to Common Council, 10/21/03 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Tompkins County Bar Association Remarks, 10/22/03 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - FR-NYPRO Dinner, Lankton, 10/22/03 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Kroll Foremost Benefactor Ceremony, 10/23/03 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Cornell Entrepreneur of 2003, Jules Kroll, 10/23/03 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - FHTR Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 10/24/03 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 400 Club Breakfast, 10/24/03 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Lynch/Weiss Campus Visit, 10/25/03 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Seattle All-Alumni Reception, 10/30/03 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Institute for Community College Development Statement, 10/2003 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Oregon All-Alumni Reception, 10/28/03 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Princeton Pre-Game All- Alumni Celebration, 11/01/03 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Princeton Event-Steve Fillo, 11/01/03 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Ithaca Public Education Initiative, 11/03/03 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - EPE Program Report- President's Message, 11/2003 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - NAACP/LDF, 11/06/03 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - PCCW Greeting, 11/07/03 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - "Lehman at Lehman" Lehman Brothers Reception, 11/12/03 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Alumni Campus Visit, 11/14/03 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Atkinson-Updike Dinner, 11/18/03 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Rotary Club of Ithaca, 11/19/03 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Iftaar Banquet, 11/19/03 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - CUFF Forum, 11/19/03 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Fall Department Chair Session, 11/20/03 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - CALS Fall Advisory Council Meeting, 11/20/03 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Durland Memorial Lecture, 11/20/03 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - CAPE Presentation, 11/20/03 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Reception Hosted by Leslie and Barbara Kaplan, 11/21/03 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Cornell Black Alumni Association, 11/22/03 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Cornell in Philly, 11/22/03 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - New Life Sciences Initiative, Genomics Initiative, 11/25/03 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Christmas Card, 11/2003 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Dinner Hosted by Helen and Robert Appel, 12/10/03 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Celebration of January 2004 Graduates, 12/20/03 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Sheila Johnson Introduction, 01/14/04 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Employee Assembly Staff Event, 01/15/04 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Major Gifts Committee Meeting, 01/21/04 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - President's Circle Dinner, 01/21/04 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Land Grant Committee, 01/22/04 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Joint Meeting - BOT/BOO, 01/23/04 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Pan Asian New Year Banquet, 01/24/04 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - CACO Luncheon, 01/24/04 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Student Leadership Keynote, 01/31/04 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Chamber Annual Dinner, 01/29/04 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - ISCOL Program Quote, 01/2004 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Downtown Groundbreaking, 02/02/04 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Washington Reception, 02/03/04 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Academic Assembly- Library, 02/05/04 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Testimony-Albany, 02/05/04 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Games Reception, 02/05/04 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - KAO-Human Services, 02/05/04 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Senior Class Campaign Kick-off Reception, 02/10/04 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Kosher Dining Hall Reopening, 02/11/04 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Dinner Hosted by Kevin and Lisa McGovern, 02/13/04 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Investment Committee Meeting, 02/14/04 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Cornell Clubs of Eastern Florida and Gold Coast, 02/15/04 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Cornell Club of Greater Miami, 02/16/04 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Cornell Alumni Association of Southwest Florida, 02/17/04 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Cornell Club of Sarasota- Manatee, 02/18/04 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Cornell Club of Tulsa, 02/19/04 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Dallas All-Alumni Reception, 02/20/04 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Houston All-Alumni Reception, 02/21/04 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Syracuse MDA, 02/26/04 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Florida Itinerary, 02/2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bill Gates Visit, 02/25/04 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - United Way Campaign Celebration, 03/05/04 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - CIPA Presentation, 03/05/04 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bridging the Rift Center Groundbreaking Ceremony, 03/10/04 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Award Recognition Ceremony, 03/11/04 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dyson Surprise Birthday Toast, 03/12/04 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - PCCW Annual Meeting Reception and Dinner, 03/12/04 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Retirees Association, 03/18/04 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - AAU Testimony-NSF/NASA, 03/25/04 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - CALS Alumni Centennial Forum Luncheon, 04/03/04 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Johnson Art Opening, 04/03/04 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Jospin Toast, 04/07/04 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bartels World Affairs Fellowship Lecture Introduction, 04/12/04 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ithaca Downtown Partnership, 04/13/04 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dinner in Honor of Sam and Gene Johnson, 04/14/04 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Johnson School 20th Anniversary Introduction of S. I. Weill, 04/14/04 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Johnson School 20th Anniversary Intro of Steve Friedman, 04/15/04 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Hatfield Program in Economic Education Public Address, 04/15/04 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Perkins Prize Ceremony, 04/21/04 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Jennie Farley Office Professionals Celebration, 04/21/04 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - New York City Spring Tower Club Recognition Dinner, 04/23/04 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - eCornell Taping, 04/2004 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Los Angeles All-Alumni Luncheon, 04/25/04 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - San Diego All-Alumni \ Reception, 04/26/04 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Lunch with Cornell Silicon Valley Advisors, 04/28/04 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - CSV - New Century Drivers, 04/28/04 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Land Grant-Francille, 04/30/04 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Parents Campus Visit, 04/30/04 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Library Advisory Council Lunch, 05/03/04 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Retiring Faculty Reception, 05/06/04 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Economics Conference, 05/07/04 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Liberty (NY) Economic Development Summit, 05/08/04 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Foremost Benefactor Ceremony for B.H. Kaplan and L. Kaplan, 05/11/04 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Distinguished Faculty Reception, 05/11/04 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Club of Wisconsin All-Alumni Reception, 05/13/04 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Cornell Club of Chicago All- Alumni Reception, 05/14/04 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Law School Convocation, 05/16/04 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - House II Groundbreaking, West Campus, 05/17/04 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Rochester Undergraduate Business Program Luncheon, 05/19/04 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Rochester All-Alumni Reception, 05/19/04 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Meetings in Rochester, 05/19/04 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Staff Graduation Reception, 05/21/04 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - BOCES Pre-Meeting, 05/21/04 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Ambulatory Care Groundbreaking, WMC, 05/25/04 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Merrill Presidential Scholars Breakfast and Panel Discussion, 05/26/04 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Rawlings Green Dedication, 05/28/04 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - 2004 Senior Class Campaign Reception, 05/28/04 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Trustee Dinner, Willard Straight Hall, 05/28/04 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 05/29/04 Reception and Senior Convocation with Bill Clinton (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - D.U.M. Hooding, K. Okun, 05/29/04 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Ph.D. Ceremony, 05/29/04 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Trustee Reception and Dinner Honoring Newly Tenured Faculty, 05/29/04 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - The Baccalaureate Service, 05/30/04 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Commencement Ideas, 05/2004 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Weill Commencement, 06/01/05 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Class of '49 Dinner, 06/12/04 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Cooperative Extension Banquet, K.Okun, 06/02/04 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Weill Commencement, 06/02/04 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - National Academy of Engineering Welcome, 06/03/04 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Service Recognition Dinner, 06/07/04 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Schoellkopf Groundbreaking, 06/10/04 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Classes of 1929, 1934, and 1939 Combined Reception, 06/10/04 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Class of 1944 Dinner, 06/10/04 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Olin Lecture, Dr. Edward T. Lu, 06/11/04 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Reception Honoring James and Ronetta McClure, 06/11/04 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Class of 1974 Informal Town Hall Meeting, 06/11/04 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Class of 1959 Reception, 06/11/04 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Class of 1954 Dinner, 06/11/04 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - State of the University Address, 06/12/04 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Class of 1964 40th Reunion Lunch, 06/12/04 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Africana Studies and Research Center Groundbreaking, 06/12/04 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Class of 1979 Dinner, 06/12/04 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Cornell Club of Washington Father's Day Picnic, 06/20/04 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Hong Kong Donor Recognition Dinner, 07/03/04 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Remarks at Infosys, 07/07/04 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Cornell Club of Singapore Reception, 07/05/04 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Cornell Club of Beijing Reception, 06/28/04 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - All Alumni and Parent Event in India, 07/09/04 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Cornell Club of Hong Kong Reception and Dinner, 07/02/04 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Hong Kong Parents Committee Barbecue, 07/04/04 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Cornell Connections to China, 07/2004 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Administrative Management Institute, 07/25/04 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Native American Day at The New York State Fair, 09/03/04 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Foremost Benefactor Ceremony In honor of J.W. and J.R. Carter, 09/11/04 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Meinig Family Dinner Toast, 09/11/04 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Iscol Lecture in Public Service, William Shore Introduction, 09/14/04 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Community Leaders Brunch, 09/18/04 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Atkinson Forum, 09/18/04 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Presidential Councilors Annual Meeting, 09/20/04 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dinner Hosted by Donald and Priscilla Miller, 09/23/04 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Reflections on The Call To Engagement, Draft, 09/2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - JP Morgan, 09/23/04 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - United Way, Email, Pre-mail, 09/2004 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate Council, 10/01/04 (Box 3, Folder 5a)
  - Law School Advisory Council, 10/01/04 (Box 3, Folder 5b)
  - Biomedical Engineering Celebration, 10/04/04 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - N.L.S.I. Advisory Council, 10/05/04 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NanoScale 25th Anniversary Luncheon, 10/06/04 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Duffield Hall Dedication, 10/06/04 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Engineering Fall Advisory Council Meeting, 10/07/04 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Jeff Hawkins Introduction, 10/07/04 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Luncheon in Honor of Duffield Hall Donors, 10/07/04 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - West Campus Council, 10/08/04 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - The Ethic and Spirit of Capitalism, 10/08/04 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Employee Open Forum, 10/14/04 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Entrepreneur of the Year, Steve Belkin, 10/14/04 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Opening of the ILR School's Garden Avenue Complex, 10/15/04 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Frank H.T. Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Awards Dinner, 10/15/04 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Foremost Benefactor Ceremony In Honor of Roy R. Payne, Jr., 10/16/04 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Beta Theta Pi 125th Anniversary Reception, 10/16/04 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Mock Election, Senate Debate, 10/19/04 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Introduction for Sandy Berger, 10/21/04 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Introduction for Sheryl Wudunn Lecture, 10/21/04 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Dedication of the Lewis Lecture Hall in Goldwin Smith Hall, 10/22/04 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Introduction of John Cleese, 10/22/04 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - First Year Family Weekend Lunch, 10/23/04 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Fall 400 Club Breakfast, 10/25/04 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Byrdcliffe Opening Dinner at the Johnson Museum, 10/23/04 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Johnson School Hall of Honor Introduction for Roy H. Park Jr., 10/27/04 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Alice Cook House Dedication and Beck Center Dedication, 10/28/04 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Joint Annual Meeting, Trustees and Council Members, 10/29/04 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - State of the University, 10/29/04 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Cornell Fund Kick-Off Breakfast, 10/30/04 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - CyberTower Taping, 11/01/04 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Fraternity and Sorority Affairs Faculty Appreciation Reception, 11/02/04 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Singapore-Hotel Joint Program, 11/02/04 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Dinner Hosted by Jay and Eileen McManus Walker, 11/03/04 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Club of Boston All- Alumni Reception, 11/04/04 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Lynch/Weiss Campus Visit, 11/06/04 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Alumni Parents Campus Visit, 11/05/04 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Tsinghua University, 11/08/04 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Peking University, 11/09/04 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Cornell Club of Shanghai Buffet Reception, 11/09/04 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Cornell Club of Japan Buffet Reception, 11/11/04 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - German-American Dialogue on the Future of the University, 11/13/04 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - N.E.E.S. Facility Opening, 11/15/04 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Ethics, Globalization, and Hunger- H.E. Babcock Workshop, 11/18/04 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Area Congregations Together Thanksgiving Service, 11/21/04 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Tenth Annual Trustees' Cup Brunch, 11/20/04 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Dale Corson Luncheon, 12/01/04 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - AA&P Reception, 12/13/04 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Wilson Foundation, 12/16/04 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Transnational University Clips, 12/2004 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - January Graduate Recognition Event/Winter Commencement, 12/18/04 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Cornell Bound Letter, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Letter to Parents, Reed College Sample, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Welcome Reception for New Students, 01/17/05 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Celebration, 01/17/05 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Major Gifts Committee, 01/19/05 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - President's Circle Dinner, 01/19/05 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - CACO 100th Annual Mid- Winter Meeting and Luncheon, 01/22/05 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - CACO 100th Anniversary Gala, 01/22/05 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Big Red Phonathon Semester Kickoff, 01/24/05 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Annual Meeting of the Parents Fund Committee, 02/03/05 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Senior Class Campaign Kick- off Reception, 02/08/05 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - ROTC Appreciation Luncheon, 02/11/05 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Commemoration- Yolanda King, 02/15/05 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Rotary Club of Ithaca, 02/16/05 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Investment Committee, 02/26/05 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Dinner Hosted by Kevin and Lisa McGovern, 02/26/05 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Dinner Hosted by Alan and Elizabeth Harris, 03/01/05 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Club of Sarasota- Manatee All-Alumni Dinner, 03/02/05 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CAPS Program Quote, 03/2005 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 400 Club Breakfast, 03/07/05 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - United Way Celebration, 03/08/05 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NPR Commentary- Transnational, 03/09/05 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Foremost Benefactor Ceremony For Peter B. Orthwein, 03/09/05 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Award Recognition Ceremony, 03/10/05 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Iscol Lecture Program, 03/10/05 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Life Sciences Technology Building Groundbreaking, 03/11/05 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Eulogy for Herb Gussman, 03/14/05 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Programs Reception, 03/16/05 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Africana Center Quote, 03/16/05 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Club of London All- Alumni Reception, 03/20/05 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Club of France All- Alumni Reception, 03/22/05 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Breakfast with Alumni (Paris), 03/23/05 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Cornell in Rome Tour and All-Alumni Reception, 03/24/05 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Days Video-Opening Comments, 03/28/05 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Sustainability Conference, 03/31/05 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - PCCW Annual Meeting Reception and Dinner, 04/01/05 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 18th Durland Memorial Lecture, Ann Fudge, 04/06/05 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Dinner with Sheila Johnson, 04/11/05 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - S.C. Johnson Board of Directors Meeting and Speech, 04/13/05 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - New York City Spring Tower Club Recognition Dinner, 04/14/05 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Parents Campus Visit, 04/15/05 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Messenger Lecture, 04/15/05 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Academic Diversity Panel, 04/18/05 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - The Leadership Alliance Presidential Forum, 04/19/05 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Tanner Prize Remarks, 04/21/05 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Law School Business Practices Dinner, 04/21/05 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Geneva Experiment Station Visit, 04/25/05 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Office Professionals Lunch, 04/27/05 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Bartels World Affairs Fellowship Lecture, Dennis B. Ross, 04/27/05 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Retiring Faculty Reception, 04/28/05 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Africana Studies and Research Center Dedication, 04/29/05 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Perkins Prize, 04/29/05 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - CALS-The Golden Age of Innovation Symposium, 04/29/05 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - ROTC Awards Ceremony, 04/30/05 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Cornell Mosaic Conference Lunch, 04/30/05 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Cornell Mosaic Conference Reception and Dinner, 04/30/05 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Essential New York Symposium, 05/02/05 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Campus Community Art Connections-Nancy Cantor Intro, 05/03/05 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Reception for Graduating International Students, 05/02/05 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Kaplan Lecture, Shirin Ebadi, 05/04/05 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Excellence In Leadership Awards Dinner, 05/08/05 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Ithaca All-Alumni Reception (Folder did not come with collection), 05/05/05 (Box 4)
  - Distinguished Faculty Reception, 05/09/05 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Cornell Silicon Valley's 6th Annual Presidential Event, 05/14/05 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - San Francisco Tower Club Recognition Dinner, 05/14/05 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Foremost Benefactor Ceremony In Honor of John D. McGraw, 05/15/05 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Land Grant Committee, 05/2005 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Staff Graduates Reception, 05/20/05 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Athletic Teams Reception, 05/19/05 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Ithaca Spring Tower Club Recognition Dinner, 05/20/05 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Theory Center 20th Anniversary, 05/23/05 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Cornell Class of '44 Filming, 05/24/05 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Computing Symposium Welcome, 05/24/05 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Merrill Presidential Scholars Panel Discussion, 05/25/05 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Merrill Presidential Scholars Convocation, 05/25/05 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - 2005 Senior Class Campaign Reception, 05/27/05 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Trustee Dinner, 05/27/05 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Senior Convocation, 05/28/05 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Ph.D. Ceremony, 05/28/05 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Trustee Reception and Dinner Honoring Newly Tenured Faculty, 05/28/05 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Baccalaureate Program, 05/29/05 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Commencement 2005, 05/29/2005 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Weill Medical College, 06/01/05 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Service Recognition Dinner, 06/02/05 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Hal Craft Retirement, 06/08/05 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Commencement Volunteers, 06/08/05 (Box 4, Folder 69)